[
      {
        "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly?",
        "choice1": "Apis",
        "choice2": "Coleoptera",
        "choice3": "Formicidae",
        "choice4": "Rhopalocera",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
        "choice1": "1,233 K",
        "choice2": "5,778 K",
        "choice3": "12,130 K",
        "choice4": "101,300 K",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "'.MPG' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
        "choice1": "WordPerfect Document file",
        "choice2": "MS Office document",
        "choice3": "Animation/movie file",
        "choice4": "Image file",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question":"Brass gets discoloured in air because of the presence of which of the following gases in air?",
        "choice1": "Oxygen",
        "choice2": "Hydrogen Sulphide",
        "choice3": "Carbon dioxide",
        "choice4": "Nitrogen",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "The speed of your net access is defined in terms of...",
        "choice1": "RAM",
        "choice2": "MHz",
        "choice3": "Kbps",
        "choice4": "Megabytes",
        "answer": 3
      },
      { 
        "question": "Which country is the current champion of Uber Cup?",
        "choice1": "Japan",
        "choice2": "China",
        "choice3": "Indonesia",
        "choice4": "USA",
        "answer": 1

      },
      { 
        "question": "What is part of a database that holds only one type of information?",
        "choice1": "Report",
        "choice2": "Field",
        "choice3": "Record",
        "choice4": "File",
        "answer": 2
      },
      { 
        "question": "What's a web browser?",
        "choice1": "A kind of spider",
        "choice2": "A computer that stores WWW files",
        "choice3": "A person who likes to look at websites",
        "choice4": "A software program that allows you to access sites on the World Wide Web",
        "answer": 4
      },
      { 
        "question": "How many bits make a byte?",
        "choice1": "4",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "16",
        "choice4": "32",
        "answer": 2
      },
      { 
        "question": "Electric bulb filament is made of?",
        "choice1": "Copper",
        "choice2": "Aluminum",
        "choice3": "Lead",
        "choice4": "Tungsten",
        "answer": 4
      },
      { 
        "question": "Light year is a measurement of?",
        "choice1": "Speed of aeroplanes",
        "choice2": "Speed of light",
        "choice3": "Stellar distances",
        "choice4": "Speed of rockets",
        "answer": 3
      },
      { 
        "question": "Which are Most highly intelligent mammals?",
        "choice1": "Whales",
        "choice2": "Dolphins",
        "choice3": "Elephants",
        "choice4": "Kangaroos",
        "answer": 2
      },
      { 
        "question": "Where are the headquarters of World Chess Federation?",
        "choice1": "Switzerland",
        "choice2": "Russia",
        "choice3": "Greece",
        "choice4": "Turkey",
        "answer": 3
      },
      { 
        "question": "Which country’s national football team is nicknamed as “La Albiceleste (The White and Sky Blues)?",
        "choice1": "Uruguay",
        "choice2": "Brazil",
        "choice3": "Argentina",
        "choice4": "Italy",
        "answer": 3
      },
      { 
        "question": "Which flower does the spice saffron come from?",
        "choice1": "Orchid",
        "choice2": "Crocus",
        "choice3": "Poppy",
        "choice4": "Nasturtium",
        "answer": 2
      },
      { 
        "question": "In Indonesian and Malay cuisine what does the word ‘nasi’ refer to?",
        "choice1": "Rice",
        "choice2": "Egg",
        "choice3": "Bread",
        "choice4": "Curry",
        "answer": 1
      },
      { 
        "question": "Which French city is known for the fish stew Bouillabaisse?",
        "choice1": "Nice",
        "choice2": "Marseille",
        "choice3": "Paris",
        "choice4": "Bordeaux",
        "answer": 2
      },
      { 
        "question": "Which of these cocktails does NOT typically include gin?",
        "choice1": "Bramble",
        "choice2": "Collins",
        "choice3": "Gimlet",
        "choice4": "Cosmopolitan",
        "answer": 4
      },
      { 
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a country capital?",
        "choice1": "Berlin",
        "choice2": "Melbourne",
        "choice3": "New Delhi",
        "choice4": "London",
        "answer": 2
      }
]